<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="top_stories">Top</string>
    <string name="more_options">More Options</string>
    <string name="no_story_selected">no story selected</string>
    <string name="hacker_news">Hacker News</string>
    <string name="url_is_null">Url is null</string>
    <string name="deleted">[Deleted]</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="logout_format">Logout: %1$s</string>
    <string name="appearance">Appearance</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="user_guidelines">User Guidelines</string>
    <string name="send_feedback">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="upvote">Upvote</string>
    <string name="un_vote">UnVote</string>
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="un_favorite">UnFavorite</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="flag">Flag</string>
    <string name="un_flag">UnFlag</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="reply">Reply</string>
    <string name="new_stories">New</string>
    <string name="best_stories">Best</string>
    <string name="show_hn">Show</string>
    <string name="ask_hn">Ask</string>
    <string name="jobs">Jobs</string>
    <string name="ask_hacker_news">Ask Hacker News</string>
    <string name="show_hacker_news">Show Hacker News</string>
    <string name="updates">Updates</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="password_toggle">Password toggle</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="login_error">Login Error</string>
    <string name="invalid_username_or_password">Invalid username or password</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="hacker_news_login">Hacker News Login</string>
    <string name="hacker_news_logout">Hacker News Logout</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="an_error_occurred">A error occurred. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="back_online">Back Online</string>
    <string name="offline">Offline</string>
    <string name="expand">Expand</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="fonts">Fonts</string>
    <string name="font_size_format">Font Size: %1$d</string>
    <string name="line_spacing_format">Line Spacing: %1$d</string>
    <string name="paragraph_indent_format">Paragraph Indent: %1$d</string>
    <string name="shapes">Shapes</string>
    <string name="default_string">Default</string>
    <string name="sans_serif">Sans Serif</string>
    <string name="serif">Serif</string>
    <string name="monospace">Monospace</string>
    <string name="cursive">Cursive</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="about_us_detail_html"><![CDATA[
Dear HN,
<p><b>Hacker News</b> is an open source Kotlin Multiplatform application that interacts with the news website <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/">news.ycombinator.com</a>. The source code is available under the Apache 2.0 license <a href="https://github.com/zirman/hacker_news">here</a>.</p>
<p>For support you may contact me here <a href="mailto:monoidscorp+support@gmail.com">monoidscorp+support@gmail.com</a>.</p>
<p>I hope you enjoy using the application as much as I do writing it.</p>
Best regards,
<p style="text-align:end"><font face="cursive">Robert Chrzanowski</font></p>
]]></string>
    <string name="top_stories_shortcut_long_label">Top Stories</string>
    <string name="top_stories_shortcut_short_label">Top HN</string>
    <string name="new_stories_shortcut_long_label">New Stories</string>
    <string name="new_stories_shortcut_short_label">New HN</string>
    <string name="best_stories_shortcut_long_label">Best Stories</string>
    <string name="best_stories_shortcut_short_label">Best HN</string>
    <string name="show_hacker_news_shortcut_long_label">Show Hacker News</string>
    <string name="show_hacker_news_shortcut_short_label">Show HN</string>
    <string name="ask_hacker_news_shortcut_long_label">Ask Hacker News</string>
    <string name="ask_hacker_news_shortcut_short_label">Ask HN</string>
    <string name="jobs_shortcut_long_label">Jobs Hacker News</string>
    <string name="jobs_shortcut_short_label">Jobs HN</string>
    <string name="favorites_shortcut_long_label">Favorites HN</string>
    <string name="favorites_shortcut_short_label">Favorites</string>
    <string name="profile_shortcut_short_label">Profile</string>
    <string name="profile_shortcut_long_label">Profile</string>
    <string name="open_in_browser">Open in Browser</string>
    <string name="i_agree_html"><![CDATA[
I agree to the <i>Hacker News</i> <a href="https://www.ycombinator.com/legal/">terms of service</a> and
agree to follow the <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html">user guidelines</a>
]]></string>
    <string name="comment">Comment</string>
    <string name="login_description">Login with your HN account.</string>
    <string name="top_stories_description">Most popular stories currently.</string>
    <string name="new_stories_description">Latest stories submitted.</string>
    <string name="best_stories_description">The most upvoted stories.</string>
    <string name="show_hn_description">Show HS is for something you\'ve made that other people can play with. HN users can try it out, give you feedback, and ask questions in the thread.</string>
    <string name="ask_hn_description">Ask HN for comments.</string>
    <string name="jobs_description">These are jobs at YC startups.</string>
    <string name="favorites_description">Stories that you have favorited.</string>
    <string name="profile_description">Change your profile settings.</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="follow">Follow</string>
    <string name="unfollow">Unfollow</string>
    <string name="no_setting_selected">no setting selected</string>
    <string name="rounded">Rounded</string>
    <string name="cut">Cut</string>
    <string name="light_dark_mode">Light Dark Mode</string>
    <string name="system">System</string>
    <string name="light_mode">Light Mode</string>
    <string name="dark_mode">Dark Mode</string>
    <!-- https://news.ycombinator.com/newsfaq.html -->
    <string name="faq"><![CDATA[
<h1>Hacker News FAQ<br></h1>
<h3>Are there rules about submissions and comments?<br></h3>
<a href="newsguidelines.html">https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html</a>
<br><h3>How are stories ranked?<br></h3>
<p>The basic algorithm divides points by a power of the time since a
story was submitted. Comments in threads are ranked the same way.
<p>Other factors affecting rank include user flags, anti-abuse software,
software which demotes overheated discussions, account or site weighting,
and moderator action.
<br><h3>How is a user's karma calculated?<br></h3>
<p>Roughly, the number of upvotes on their posts minus the
number of downvotes. These don't match up exactly. Some votes are
dropped by anti-abuse software.
<br><h3>Do posts by users with more karma rank higher?<br></h3>
<p>No.
<br><h3>Why don't I see down arrows?<br></h3>
<p>There are no down arrows on stories. They appear on comments after
users reach a certain karma threshold, but never on direct replies.
<br><h3>What kind of formatting can you use in comments?<br></h3>
<p><a href="formatdoc">http://news.ycombinator.com/formatdoc</a>
<br><h3>How do I submit a question?<br></h3>
<p>Use the submit link in the top bar, and leave the url field blank.
<br><h3>How do I submit a poll?<br></h3>
<p><a href="newpoll">http://news.ycombinator.com/newpoll</a>
<br><h3>How do I make a link in a text submission?<br></h3>
<p>You can't. This is to prevent people from submitting a link
with their comments in a privileged position at the top of the
page. If you want to submit a link with comments, just submit
the link, then add a regular comment.
<br><h3>What are Ask HN and Show HN?<br></h3>
<p><a href="ask">Ask HN</a> lists questions and other text submissions.
<a href="show">Show HN</a> is for sharing your personal work and has
special <a href="showhn.html">rules</a>.
<br><h3>Why hasn't my submission appeared on Ask HN or Show HN?<br></h3>
<p>All Ask HNs appear on <a href="newest">newest</a> and <a
href="asknew">asknew</a>, and all Show HNs on <a
href="newest">newest</a> and <a href="shownew">shownew</a>, but there
is a small points threshold before a post makes it to <a
href="ask">ask</a> or <a href="show">show</a>.
<br><h3>What do green usernames mean?<br></h3>
<p>Green indicates a new account.
<br><h3>Why are some comments faded?<br></h3>
<p>Faded text means that a comment has been downvoted. You can read the comment
in normal text by clicking on its timestamp to go to its page.
<br><h3>What does [flagged] mean?<br></h3>
<p>Users flagged the post as breaking the <a href="newsguidelines.html">guidelines</a>
or otherwise not belonging on HN.
<p>Moderators sometimes also add [flagged] (though not usually on
submissions), and sometimes turn flags off when they are unfair.
<br><h3>How do I flag a comment?<br></h3>
<p>Click on its timestamp to go to its page, then click the 'flag' link
at the top. There's a small karma threshold before flag links appear.
<br><h3>What does [dead] mean?<br></h3>
<p>The post was killed by software, user flags, or moderators.
<p>Dead posts aren't displayed by default, but you can see them all
by turning on 'showdead' in your profile.
<p>If you see a [dead] post that shouldn't be dead, you can vouch for it.
Click on its timestamp to go to its page, then click 'vouch' at the
top. When enough users do this, the post is restored. There's a small
karma threshold before vouch links appear.
<br><h3>What does [deleted] mean?<br></h3>
<p>The author deleted the post, or asked us to. Unlike <a
href="#dead">dead</a> posts, these remain deleted even when showdead
is turned on.
<br><h3>Are reposts ok?<br></h3>
<p>If a story has not had significant attention in the last year or so,
a small number of reposts is ok. Otherwise we bury reposts as duplicates.
<p>Please don't delete and repost the same story. Deletion is for things
that shouldn't have been submitted in the first place.
<br><h3>Are paywalls ok?<br></h3>
<p>It's ok to post stories from sites with paywalls that have workarounds.
<p>In comments, it's ok to ask how to read an article and to help other
users do so. But please don't post complaints about paywalls. Those
are <a href="item?id=10178989">off topic</a>. More <a href="https://hn.algolia.com/?query=paywalls%20by:dang&dateRange=all&page=0&prefix=false&sort=byDate&type=comment">here</a>.
<br><h3>Can I ask people to upvote my submission?<br></h3>
<p>No. Users should vote for a story because they personally find it
intellectually interesting, not because someone has content to
promote. We penalize or ban submissions, accounts, and sites that
break this rule, so please don't.
<br><h3>Can I ask people to comment on my submission?<br></h3>
<p>No, for the same reason. It's also not in your interest: HN
readers are sensitive to this and will detect it, flag it,
and use unkind words like 'spam'.
<br><h3>Can I post a job ad?<br></h3>
<p>Please don't post job ads as submissions to HN.
<p>A regular "Who Is Hiring?" thread appears on the first weekday of each
month (or Jan 2). Most job ads are welcome there. Only an account called
<a href="submitted?id=whoishiring">whoishiring</a> is allowed to
submit the thread itself. This prevents a race to post it first.
<p>Another kind of job ad is reserved for YC-funded startups. These
appear on the front page, but are not stories: they have no vote arrows,
points, or comments. They begin part-way down and fall steadily.
Only one is on the front page at a time. The rest are listed
at <a href="jobs">jobs</a>.
<br><h3>What's the relationship between YC and HN?<br></h3>
<p><a href="https://ycombinator.com">Y Combinator</a> owns and funds HN. The
HN team is <a href="https://venturebeat.com/2015/09/29/y-combinator-spins-out-hacker-news-to-give-it-full-editorial-independence/">editorially</a> <a href="https://blog.ycombinator.com/two-hn-announcements/">independent</a>.
<p>HN gives three features to YC:
job ads (see <a href="#jobads">above</a>) and startup <a href="launches">launches</a>
get placed on the front page, and YC founder names
are displayed to other YC alumni in orange.
<br><h3>Are negative stories about YC suppressed on HN?<br></h3>
<p>No, we moderate <a href="https://hn.algolia.com/?query=moderate%20less%20not%20more%20yc%20by:dang&dateRange=all&page=0&prefix=false&sort=byDate&type=comment">less, not more</a>, when YC or a YC startup is the topic.
The good will of the community is worth more than any story.
<br><h3>Why can't I post a comment to a thread?<br></h3>
<p>Threads are closed to new comments after two weeks, or if the
submission has been killed by software, moderators, or user flags.
<br><h3>Why is A ranked below B even though A has more points
and is newer?<br></h3>
<p>You can't derive rank from votes and time alone. See "How are stories ranked?" above.
<br><h3>In my profile, what is delay?<br></h3>
<p>It gives you time to edit your comments before they appear to others.
Set it to the number of minutes you'd like. The maximum is 10.
<br><h3>In my profile, what is noprocrast?<br></h3>
<p>It's a way to help you prevent yourself from spending too much time on
HN. If you turn it on you'll only be allowed to visit the site for
maxvisit minutes at a time, with gaps of minaway minutes in between.
The defaults are 20 and 180, which would let you view the site for 20
minutes at a time, and then not allow you back in for 3 hours.
<br><h3>How do I reset my password?<br></h3>
<p>If you have an email address in your profile, you can do that
<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/forgot?id=">here</a>. If
you haven't, email hn@ycombinator.com for help.
<br><h3>Can I change my username?<br></h3>
<p>Yes. Email hn@ycombinator.com and we'll help.
<br><h3>Can I delete my account?<br></h3>
<p>We try not to delete entire account histories because that would gut
the threads the account had participated in. However, we care about
protecting individual users and take care of privacy requests every
day, so if we can help, please email hn@ycombinator.com. We don't want
anyone to get in trouble from anything they posted to HN. More <a
href="item?id=23623799">here</a>.
<br><h3>My IP address seems to be banned. How can I unban it?<br></h3>
<p>If you request many pages quickly, your IP address might get
banned.
This <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4761102">self-serve
unbanning procedure</a> works most of the time. If not, email hn@ycombinator.com.
]]></string>
    <!-- https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html -->
    <string name="guidelines"><![CDATA[
<h1>Hacker News Guidelines<br></h1>
<h3>What to Submit<br></h3>
<p>On-Topic: Anything that good hackers would find interesting. That includes
more than hacking and startups. If you had to reduce it to a sentence,
the answer might be: anything that gratifies one's intellectual
curiosity.</p>
<p>Off-Topic: Most stories about politics, or crime, or sports, or
celebrities, unless they're evidence of some interesting new
phenomenon. Videos of pratfalls or disasters, or cute animal pictures.
If they'd cover it on TV news, it's probably off-topic.
<br><h3>In Submissions<br></h3>
<p>Please don't do things to make titles stand out, like using uppercase
or exclamation points, or saying how great an article is. It's
implicit in submitting something that you think it's important.
<p>Please submit the original source.  If a post reports on
something found on another site, submit the latter.
<p>Please don't use HN primarily for promotion. It's ok to post
your own stuff part of the time, but the primary use of the site
should be for curiosity.
<p>If the title includes the name of the site, please take it out,
because the site name will be displayed after the link.
<p>If the title contains a gratuitous number or number + adjective,
we'd appreciate it if you'd crop it.  E.g. translate "10 Ways
To Do X" to "How To Do X," and "14 Amazing Ys" to "Ys."  Exception:
when the number is meaningful, e.g. "The 5 Platonic Solids."
<p>Otherwise please use the original title, unless it
is misleading or linkbait; don't editorialize.
<p>If you submit a video or pdf, please warn us by appending
[video] or [pdf] to the title.
<p>Please don't post on HN to ask or tell us something. Send it
to hn@ycombinator.com.
<p>Please don't delete and repost. Deletion is for things
that shouldn't have been submitted in the first place.
<p>Don't solicit upvotes, comments, or submissions. Users should vote and
comment when they run across something they personally find
interesting&mdash;not for promotion.
<br><h3>In Comments<br></h3>
<p>Be kind. Don't be snarky. Converse curiously; don't cross-examine.
Edit out swipes.
<p>Comments should get more thoughtful and substantive,
not less, as a topic gets more divisive.
<p>When disagreeing, please reply to the argument instead of calling
names. "That is idiotic; 1 + 1 is 2, not 3" can be shortened to "1 + 1
is 2, not 3."
<p>Please don't fulminate. Please don't sneer, including at the rest of
the community.
<p>Please respond to the strongest plausible interpretation of what
someone says, not a weaker one that's easier to criticize. Assume good
faith.
<p>Eschew flamebait. Avoid generic tangents. Omit internet tropes.
<p>Please don't post shallow dismissals, especially of other people's
work. A good critical comment teaches us something.
<p>Please don't use Hacker News for political or ideological battle. It
tramples curiosity.
<p>Please don't comment on whether someone read an article. "Did you
even read the article? It mentions that" can be shortened to "The
article mentions that".
<p>Please don't pick the most provocative thing in an article or post to
complain about in the thread. Find something interesting to respond to
instead.
<p>Throwaway accounts are ok for sensitive information, but please don't
create accounts routinely. HN is a community&mdash;users should have an
identity that others can relate to.
<p>Please don't use uppercase for emphasis.  If you want to emphasize
a word or phrase, put *asterisks* around it and it will get
italicized.
<p>Please don't post insinuations about astroturfing, shilling,
brigading, foreign agents, and the like. It degrades discussion
and is usually mistaken. If you're worried about abuse, email
hn@ycombinator.com and we'll look at the data.
<p>Please don't complain that a submission is inappropriate. If a story
is spam or off-topic, flag it. Don't feed egregious comments by
replying; <a href="newsfaq.html#cflag">flag</a> them instead. If you
flag, please don't also comment that you did.
<p>Please don't complain about tangential annoyances&mdash;e.g.
article or website formats, name collisions, or back-button breakage.
They're too common to be interesting.
<p>Please don't comment about the voting on comments. It never does any
good, and it makes boring reading.
<p>Please don't post comments saying that HN is turning into Reddit.
It's
<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=1524184">a</a>
<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=926703">semi</a>-<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=633099">noob</a>
<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=582513">illusion</a>,
<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=289254">as</a>
<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=253657">old</a>
<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=66057">as</a>
<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=60767">the</a>
<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=13852">hills</a>.
]]></string>
</resources>
